{
    "question": "1. How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?",
    "choices": ["msg('Hello World')", "msgBox('Hello World');", "alertBox('Hello World');", "alert('Hello World');"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
}, {
    "question": "2. How to empty an array in JavaScript?",
    "choices": ["arrayList[]", "arrayList(0)", "arrayList.length=0", "arrayList.len(0)"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
}, {
    "question": "3. What function to add an element at the begining of an array and one at the end?",
    "choices": ["push,unshift", "unshift,push", "first,push", "unshift,last"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
}, {
    "question": "4. What will this output? var a = [1, 2, 3]; console.log(a[6]);",
    "choices": ["undefined", "0", "prints nothing", "Syntax error"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
}, {
    "question": "5. What would following code return? console.log(typeof typeof 1);",
    "choices": ["string", "number", "Syntax error", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
},{
	"question": "6. Which software company developed JavaScript?",
    "choices": ["Mozilla", "Netscape", "Sun Microsystems", "Oracle"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
},{
	"question": "7. What would be the result of 3+2+'7'?",
    "choices": ["327", "12", "14", "57"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
},{
	"question": "8. Look at the following selector: $('div'). What does it select?",
    "choices": ["The first div element", "The last div element", "All div elements", "Current div element"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
},{
	"question": "9. How can a value be appended to an array?",
    "choices": ["arr(length).value;", "arr[arr.length]=value;", "arr[]=add(value);", "None of these"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
},{
	"question": "10. What does HTML stand for?",
    "choices": ["Hyper Test Markup Language", "Hyper Text Markup Language", "Hourly Tether Makeup Language", "Hyperspace Tether Markup Language"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
},{
	"question": "11. What does a boolean method return?",
    "choices": ["An if/else statement", "A true/false statement", "A string of values", "An arrow to the knee"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
},{
	"question": "12. In HTML, where would the CSS file be linked?",
    "choices": ["<body></body>", "<script></script>", "<head></head>", "<div></div>"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
}